(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-22T22:51:15.804061",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
僕たちは配信アプリ「ホロキャス」で活動する配信者。
We're streamers active on the streaming app HoloCast.
突然画面に吸い込まれて、アプリと繋がる謎の世界「ホロキャス界」に来ちゃった！
Suddenly sucked into our screens, we ended up in the mysterious world connected to the app, the HoloCast Realm!
そこでは、現実で苦しむ人の魂が怪物化してしまう現象「ユメオチ」が起こっていた。
There, a phenomenon called Yumeochi was occurring, where souls of suffering people turned into monsters.
怪物コラプサーを倒して、みんなの魂を取り戻さないと！
We have to defeat the monster Collapsars and rescue everyone's souls!
そして、魔法少女に変身して戦うことになった。
And so, we transformed into magical girls to fight.
みんなの心を助けて、夢を応援するの！
We save everyone's hearts and cheer on their dreams!
それが...
That is...
魔法少女ホロウィッチ！
Magical Girl holoWitches!
今日はスペシャルハロウィンステージ！
Today is a special Halloween stage!
ホロキャスの人気配信者が多数出演！
Featuring many popular streamers from HoloCast!
さらに、今ときめく超人気歌手のカノンさんも参加する超・超豪華イベント！
Plus, the super popular singer Kanon is also joining this super lavish event!
で、その超豪華イベントのオープニングアクトをうちの6人が担当することになって...
And so, the six of us were chosen to do the opening act for this super lavish event...
せっかくだし、みんなでホロウィッチの衣装を着てドカンと派手に盛り上げちゃおうかなーって。
We thought, since we're here, why not wear our holoWitches outfits and really hype things up with a bang?
でも、いいのかな？
But is that really okay?
魔法とか妖精とか、一応ナイショなんだけど...
Magic and fairies are supposed to be a secret, though...
今日はハロウィンだから仮装ってことにすれば...
Since it's Halloween today, if we just call it costumes...
なんとかなるなら！
If that works out!
そうそう。
Right, right.
てか、そろそろ準備した方が良くない？
Wait, shouldn't we start getting ready soon?
そうだね！
You're right!
よーし、気合入れていきますか！
Alright, let's gear up and get to it!
トリック・オア...
Trick or...
トリート！
Treat!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー 足りないでしょ
Craving, craving, craving, you still need more, right?
こっちおいで 遊ぼうよ！
Come over here, let's play!
キラキラしていたい 楽しくいられるために全力
Wanting to stay sparkling, going all out just to have fun!
イライラしてたら 魂抜ける もったいない！
Getting irritated makes your soul drain out, what a waste!
「どうしたら喜んでくれるかな」ばっか
Always thinking, "What would make them happy?"
思いついては即行動 スマイルハンター
Acting as soon as an idea hits, a Smile Hunter!
こっそり君のツボ ピンポイント
Secretly pinpointing what hits your sweet spot,
撃ち抜いちゃう 成功！
sniping it right on target—success!
魔法だもん 愛の呪文
It's magic after all, a spell of love!
フルキャストコンサート
A full-cast concert,
まだまだ仕掛けちゃえ！
let's set off even more surprises!
あっという間に つかまえた！
Caught you in the blink of an eye!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅーシンドローム
Craving, craving, craving syndrome!
いたずらからの ハピネス
Happiness born from pranks!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅーしたらキュン
Craving, craving, craving, and your heart flutters!
照れ隠しで スマイルニッ
A big grin to hide the embarrassment!
年中無休 carnival 好き重なれば
365-day carnival, when love overlaps,
年中無休 carnival お祭り
365-day carnival, a festival!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー 足りない！
Craving, craving, craving, it's not enough!
こっちおいで 遊ぼうよ！
Come over here, let's play!
虜にしちゃう ほらね？
I'll make you fall for me, see?
プランは完璧！
The plan is perfect!
アドレナリン どばどば出させちゃうんです！
Making adrenaline gush out in torrents!
ここをこうしたらみんながびっくりして～
If we do this here, everyone will be so surprised...
ちょっと待って！私の出番は？
Hold on a second! What about my turn?
つまりどういうこと？？？
What does that mean???
もうはちゃめちゃだ～！
It's total chaos now~!
始まりは違っても 同じ道ゆく
Even if we started differently, we walk the same path.
ピーキーだって集まれば つまり最強じゃん？
Even if we're eccentric, when we assemble, aren't we the strongest?
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅーシンドローム
Craving, craving, craving syndrome!
高鳴りすぎて発熱
Throbbing so hard I'm running a fever!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅーしとこ？
Craving, craving, craving, shall we stay like this?
とっておきの ウィンクはい！
Here's a special wink, high-five!
異世界から見せたい
Wanting to show you from another world
両手いっぱいの愛
An armful of love
こんなにも近くにいるよ
I'm right here this close to you!
年中無休で笑いたい
Wanting to smile 365 days a year,
君と笑い合いたいの
wanting to share smiles with you!
やんややっきゃっきゃしていたら いつつの間にか救えちゃう
While having fun and making noise, before we know it, we save everyone!
幸せすぎて困っちゃう
So happy it's almost overwhelming!
つかまえたら離さない
Once I catch you, I won't let go!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅーシンドローム
Craving, craving, craving syndrome!
いたずらからの ハピネス
Happiness born from pranks!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅーしたらキュン
Craving, craving, craving, and your heart flutters!
照れ隠しで スマイルニッ
A big grin to hide the embarrassment!
年中無休 carnival 好き重なれば
365-day carnival, when love overlaps,
年中無休 carnival お祭り
365-day carnival, a festival!
トリック・オア・トリート！
Trick or treat!
みんな 盛り上がってるー？
Is everyone hyped up?!
ホロウィッチのオープニングアクト どうだったー？
How was Holowitch's opening act?
ここから もっともっと盛り上げていくから
We're gonna hype things up even more from here,
みんなで一緒に楽しもうね！
so let's all have fun together!
今日はわれわれ ホロキャスの配信者だけじゃなく
Today, it's not just us Holocast streamers,
あの超人気歌手 カノンさんがゲストで来てくださってまーす！
but that super popular singer, Kanon-san, is here as our guest!
カノンさん どうぞー！
Kanon-san, please come out!
トリック・オア・トリート
Trick or treat.
みんな 今日は最後まで
Everyone, until the very end today,
よろしく
please enjoy.
いやーまさかね あのカノンさんと同じステージに立てるなんて...
Wow, I really can't believe we're standing on the same stage as Kanon-san...
いやホント 憧れですよ！
Yeah, really! It's an absolute dream!
カノンさんの歌を聞くと すっごくパワーもらえるのら！
Listening to Kanon-san's singing gives me so much energy, nora!
そうそう！こんなにいただいちゃっていいんですか！？ってくらいね！
Exactly! Like, "Is it really okay for us to receive this much?!"
うんうん！めっちゃ元気出るよね！
Mm-hmm! It really brightens you up!
ありがとう なんでもないから...
Thank you. It's nothing...
次の曲は みんなも一緒に歌ってほしいのら！
For the next song, we want everyone to sing along too, nora!
君たち！遠慮しないで声出してね！声！
You guys! Don't hold back, make some noise! Make some noise!
キミの声を聞かせて
Let me hear your voice!
さあ 冒険してみない？
Come on, why don't we go on an adventure?
楽しいこと始めよう
Let's start having fun!
遊びたい 絶対！
I wanna play, absolutely!
たい！ たい！ たい！
Wanna, wanna, wanna!
あいわな
I wanna!
JOY と JOY と JOY と POP な BABY
Joy and joy and joy and pop baby!
JOY と JOY と JOY と HAPPY な PEOPLE
Joy and joy and joy and happy people!
弱虫なんかじゃない
I'm no coward,
自信ありげにピースサイン
showing a confident peace sign!
キミの瞳にキスして
Kiss your eyes
笑いたい 絶対！
and smile, absolutely!
たい！ たい！ たい！
Wanna, wanna, wanna!
あいわな
I wanna!
JOY と JOY と JOY と 勇気な BABY
Joy and joy and joy and courageous baby!
JOY と JOY と JOY と HAPPY な SAY YEAH
Joy and joy and joy and happy say yeah!
君の心はそうもっと DO DO
Your heart does, does more!
僕の心もそういっそ GOOD GOOD
And my heart feels more good, good!
はじけてるんじゃない？
Aren't we breaking out?
IT'S JOYFUL
PA-PI-PU-PE-PO BABUU~
YEA-AH!
Yeah!
JOY と JOY と JOY と POP な BABY
Joy and joy and joy and pop baby!
JOY と JOY と JOY と HAPPY な PEOPLE
Joy and joy and joy and happy people!
ドキドキしちゃうのなんでだろう
Why is my heart racing so much?
ズキズキしちゃうのなんでだろう
Why is it throbbing like this?
この指に止まるのはどんな運命なんだ
What kind of fate will land on this finger?
ぜんぶしたいな
I wanna experience it all!
じょいふるだって終わっちゃう
Even joyful times come to an end,
エブリバディいつか終わっちゃう
everybody ends someday.
いついつもしよう
Always and forever, let me be like this,
このときも最終形はきっと修正なしで
even at the final stage, surely with no corrections!
DO WE DO WE DO WE DO DO
PI-PU-PE-PO PA-PI-PU-PE 痛いっ！ とぅ たいっ！
Pi-pu-pe-po pa-pi-pu-pe, it hurts! To tai!
たい！ たい！ たい！
Wanna, wanna, wanna!
あいわな
I wanna!
JOY と JOY と JOY と 勇気な BABY
Joy and joy and joy and courageous baby!
JOY と JOY と JOY と HAPPY な SAY YEAH
Joy and joy and joy and happy say yeah!
君の心はそうもっと DO DO
Your heart does, does more!
僕の心もそういっそ GOOD GOOD
And my heart feels more good, good!
はじけてるんじゃない？
Aren't we breaking out?
IT'S JOYFUL
PA-PI-PU-PE-PO BABUU~
JOY
みんなー！
Everyone!
一緒に歌ってくれてありがとう〜！
Thank you so much for singing along with us!
いや〜、よかったね〜！
Man, that was so great!
会場がね、一体になったって感じでね〜！
It really felt like the whole venue united as one!
よかったよかった！
That was great, that was great!
テンションあがるわ、これ！
This really gets my energy up!
さ、さーて次は！
N-Now then, up next...
いよいよ、かなたんさんに歌っていただきます！
...Kanata-san is finally going to sing for us!
君... 大丈夫？
Are you... okay?
なになに！？ 何の音！？
What was that!? What's that sound!?
あれ？
Huh?
あわ？ あわって...
Bubbles? Bubbles...?
まさか...
Could it be...?
取れないんだけど！
I can't get this off!
なにこれ！？
What is this?!
ちょ、ちょ、ちょ、ちょ！
W-W-Wait a minute!
なになに！？ どういうこと！？
What is this!? What's going on!?
コラプサーだ！
It's a Corruptor!
ですよね！ どう考えてもね！
I knew it! No matter how you look at it!
コラプサー... やっぱり
A Corruptor... Just as I thought.
痛い痛い痛い！
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
怖い怖い怖い！
Scary, scary, scary!
えっ、えっと... こういう時は...
U-Um... at times like this...
ト、トリック・オア・トリート！
T-Trick or treat!
何もかも違うだろ
Everything about that is wrong.
あがねー！ 魂が逆になってるよ！
Oh no! Her soul is coming out backwards!
フブさん！
Fubu-san!
出てる出てる！ 魂の尾っぽが出てる！
It's coming out! The tail of her soul is sticking out!
よいしょー！
Heave-ho!
だが、コラプサーが出てくるってことは...
But if a Corruptor is appearing here...
ユメオチしてる人がいるんだ！ たぶん...
Someone is falling into despair! Probably...
ミオ先輩！
Mio-senpai!
ミオちゃん！
Mio-chan!
ご、ごめん...
I-I'm sorry...
うち... うち、本当は...
I... I actually...
ハロウィンのカボチャが怖くてダメなのー！
I'm terrified of Halloween pumpkins!
えっ？
Eh?
ちっちゃい頃、パパがハロウィンであれ被って帰ってきて...
When I was little, my dad came home wearing one of those for Halloween...
ただいまー
[Dad]: I'm home~
うち、パパがカボチャに食べられちゃったんだって思っちゃって...
I thought my dad had been eaten by a pumpkin...
ハッピーハロウィーン！！
[Dad]: Happy Halloween!!
それから...
Ever since then...
どうしても...
No matter what...
ハロウィンのカボチャだけは、無理なの〜！
...Halloween pumpkins are just too much for me!
いやーー！
Nooo!
チェンジ！
Change!
ガーディアン・アーム！
Guardian Arm!
ミコメロ・ロッド！
Mikomelo Rod!
キャンディ・パラソル！
Candy Parasol!
ガンバリナー！
Ganbarina!
スノーフレーク・セイバー！
Snowflake Saber!
吹雪丸！
Fubukimaru!
ここは任せて、ミオ！
Leave this to us, Mio!
みんな...
Everyone...
魔法、みんなに見せちゃうけど、いいよね！
We're showing everyone our magic, but that's okay, right?!
うん！ そんなこと言ってらんないし！
Yeah! We don't have time to worry about that!
だよね！ ユメオチした人を助ける、それが...
That's right! Saving people who've fallen into despair, that is...
魔法少女、ホロウィッチ！
Magical Girls, HoloWitches!
この手を差し伸べて 掴んで 握る！
Reach out this hand, grab on, hold tight!
天使のホロ！ 魔法少女かなた！
Angel Holo! Magical Girl Kanata!
みんなの願いを咲かせる祈り！
A prayer to make everyone's wishes bloom!
巫女のホロ！ 魔法少女みこ！
Shrine Maiden Holo! Magical Girl Miko!
甘い幸せ お裾分け！
Sharing a slice of sweet happiness!
姫のホロ！ 魔法少女ルーナ！
Princess Holo! Magical Girl Luna!
煌めくお宝 ドッキュン！
Sparkling treasure, bang!
海賊のホロ！ 魔法少女マリン！
Pirate Holo! Magical Girl Marine!
心踊らすトリックスター！
The heart-thrilling trickster!
狐のホロ！ 魔法少女フブキ！
Fox Holo! Magical Girl Fubuki!
積もり重なる純白の愛
Piling up, pure white love...
雪のホロ
Holo of snow...
魔法少女ラミィ！
Magical Girl Lamy!
ホロウィッチ！
HoloWitches!
フルキャスト！
Full Cast!
行くよー！
Here I go!
はい！ はい！ はい！
Ha! Ha! Ha!
パンプ... 敵じゃないよ、仲間だよ
Pump... I'm not an enemy, I'm a friend!
コン！
Kon!
やめな！
Stop it!
せい！
Sei!
おいおいおい...
Hey, hey, hey...
な、なんかこれまずくない？ どんどん強くなってる...
W-Wait, isn't this bad? They're getting stronger...
みんなが奴らを倒すより、不安と恐れが膨れ上がる方が早いみたい！
Anxiety and fear are growing faster than everyone can defeat them!
そんな...
No way...
うちのせい...
It's my fault...
うちが... あんなもの怖いって思っちゃうせいで...
Because I... felt scared of things like that...
そんなこと...
That's not...
わかってるの...
I know...
おかしいよね... あんなのが、こんな、どうしようもなく怖いなんて...
It's weird, right? Being so helplessly scared of something like that...
だから... 今日も我慢して、頑張ろうって思ったのに...
That's why... I told myself I'd endure it and try my best today too...
でも... でもやっぱり...
But... But still...
おかしくなんてないよ。
There's nothing weird about it.
カノンさん...
Qon-san...
誰にだって、苦手なものがある。怖いもの、嫌いなもの。
Everyone has weaknesses. Things they fear, things they dislike.
人に「なんでそんなものが？」って言われても、どうしようもないことって、やっぱりあるよ。
Even if others ask 'Why are you afraid of that?', there are just things you can't help.
そうだよ！
That's right!
何が苦手とか何が怖いとかは関係なくて！
It doesn't matter what you're bad at or afraid of!
大事なのは今、ミオちゃんが辛いって思ってるってことだから！
What matters is that right now, Mio-chan is suffering!
遠慮しないで...
Don't hold back...
頼ってほしいのら！
We want you to rely on us!
だって、そうやってさ...
Because, after all...
うちら、お互い様じゃん！
we support each other!
誰かの辛さや誰かの苦手は...
Someone's pain or someone's weakness...
他の誰かがカバーする！
will be covered by someone else!
お互いそうやって...
That's how we've all...
やってきたんだから！ 今だって...
gotten by! Even now...
こんなに頑張れる！
we can fight this hard!
ホロウィッチ... コラップサーは...
HoloWitches... The Corruptors are...
夢落ちした人の恐れと不安から生まれ...
born from the fear and anxiety of those who fell into Dreamfall...
その心を深く沈ませる。
sinking their hearts deep down into darkness.
夢落ちって...
Dreamfall...?
どうしてそれを...？
How do you know that...?
でも... 私は知ってる。
But... I know.
君たちなら... ホロウィッチなら...
If it's you... If it's the HoloWitches...
辛い、苦しい、悲しい、きつい...
Painful, agonizing, sad, tough...
そんな、自分一人の力じゃ抜け出せない暗闇の中にいても...
Even in a darkness so deep you can't escape on your own...
夢へ... 光を届けてくれる！
you will deliver light... to their dreams!
任せて！
Leave it to us!
さあ、みんな。
Now, everyone.
ホロウィッチが戦ってくれる。
The HoloWitches are fighting for us.
では、私達にできるのは？
So, what is it that we can do?
そう... 私達の声で...
That's right... With our voices...
思いで！
With our feelings!
彼女たちを応援することだ！
To cheer them on!
いざ！ トリック・オア・トリート！
Now then! Trick or Treat!
仮装狂騒曲
[Song: Masquerade Rhapsody]
あれよと言う間に 飲み込まれる
橙色のタイダルウェーブ 夜行夜光
Swallowed up in the blink of an eye,
an orange tidal wave, nocturnal night lights.
ハンドメイドから オーダーメイドまで
仕掛ける大流行
From handmade to custom order,
launching a grand craze.
本物から偽物まで まとめ大集合
From the real deal to fakes,
a massive gathering altogether.
揃いも揃って不揃いの世界観に
お揃いの幼稚さに辟易な恒例
In a world view where all are misfits,
tired of the standard matching childishness.
催しの奴隷 夜通し踊れ
条例処刑フォーメーションで 褒美を獲れ
Slaves to the event, dance all night long,
in execution formation, claim your reward.
マーマレードが溶ける頃
キャパ以上にお道化る者
Around the time marmalade melts,
those who play the fool beyond their capacity.
チヤホヤしたりされたりが いいんでしょ？
Flattering and being flattered feels good, right?
甘い だけじゃ 物足りない give me some more
Just sweet isn't enough, give me some more.
邪気に呑まれ 制御不能
Swallowed up and out of control by malice,
好きに奪い去る 異議マイナス 陰気
Snatching away as they please, minus objections, gloom.
バイラル 意に介さず イニミニマニモ
Viral, paying no heed, eeny, meeny, miny, moe.
恐ろしや 漫ろ
How terrifying, wandering aimlessly.
浮かび上がり回る月に針が落ちる
The needle drops on the floating, revolving moon.
大きな口で笑うカボチャたちが歌う
Pumpkins with huge smiling mouths sing out.
それが合図 魔物たちが目覚め踊る
That's the signal, monsters awaken and dance!
こうなればあとは思いのまま
Once it gets like this, all that's left is to have our way.
翻弄 骨抜き danceable
Tricked, demoralized, danceable.
スケアクロウも飛び跳ね廻る
Even the scarecrow leaps and dances around.
hollow 月夜の turntable
A turntable in the hollow moonlit night.
くるくる狂おしい高まり
Spinning, spinning, a crazy surge of excitement!
We got the party night!
Anyway, enjoy the party night!
フルーティー無邪気な空気じゃ無理
A fruity, innocent vibe just won't cut it.
贅沢に清濁をチェイサーなしでいただけばヘラヘラ
Downing sweet and bitter luxury without a chaser, grinning away.
Where is my 素敵なナイト 見つからなくても既に薔薇色
Where is my wonderful knight? Even if I can't find one, it's already rose-colored.
嫉妬は見苦しいから着ぐるみに指定してから
Jealousy is unsightly, so I'll stuff it into a mascot costume...
剥いであげる身包み
...and strip away its pretense!
仮の衣装でも魂が本物ならば
Even in a temporary costume, if the soul is genuine...
魅了してイマジナリー以上
...it'll enchant you beyond imagination.
死霊生霊構わず邂逅
Spirits of the dead or living, meeting without care.
とびきりの美貌 ハッピーな非日常
Extraordinary beauty, a happy non-everyday life.
ガラパゴスに交わる異世界大交流パーティー
An otherworldly grand exchange party intersecting in Galapagos!
振り切れる鼓動
A heart beating off the charts!
悪目立ちのドラキュラもお酒を煽る
Even the flashy Dracula downs his drink!
寡黙そうなデュラハンも頭を振る
Even the quiet-looking Dullahan headbangs!
紳士的なミイラすらも服がはだける
Even the gentlemanly Mummy strips off his clothes!
どうあれど愉快全開のまま
Whatever happens, staying at full delight!
本性 露わに暴れよう
Let's expose our true nature and go wild!
その仮装も正装になる
Even those costumes will become formal wear!
狂騒曲の turntable
Turntable of the rhapsody!
あいあい愛おしい高まり
Dear, precious excitement!
hi-fi, all night all night
眠れやしない woo la la la...
Can't sleep at all, woo la la la...
fly high, all night all night
鳴り止まない woo la la la...
It won't stop ringing, woo la la la...
誇大妄想な遊び
A game of grandiose delusions.
ランタンはまるで魂 依然奇怪なジャンボリー
Lanterns are like souls, still a bizarre jamboree!
let me hear you say ハロウィン
Let me hear you say Halloween!
翻弄 骨抜き danceable
Tricked, demoralized, danceable.
スケアクロウも飛び跳ね廻る
Even the scarecrow leaps and dances around.
hollow 月夜の turntable
A turntable in the hollow moonlit night.
くるくる狂おしい高まり
Spinning, spinning, a crazy surge of excitement!
we got the party night!
anyway, enjoy the party night!
くるくる狂おしい高まり
Spinning, spinning, a crazy surge of excitement!
we got the party night night night!
ホロックス様の力が乱れている！
Lord HoloX's power is going wild!
恐れと不安が溶けていくんだ...
Our fear and anxiety are melting away...
歌の力...！みんなの声の力で...！
By the power of song...! The power of everyone's voices...!
みんな乗ってるねー！
Everyone's really getting into it!
おかげでこっちもやる気いっぱいなのナ！
Thanks to that, we're totally pumped up too!
さあ、行って！ホロウィッチ！心を苛むトリックに！
Now, go! HoloWitch! Against the trick that torments hearts!
飛び切りのトリート！
Deliver the ultimate treat!
みんな、応援ありがとう！思う存分、楽しんじゃうよ！
Everyone, thanks for the cheers! I'm going to enjoy this to my heart's content!
トリック... 一閃！
Trick... Flash!
うわー！やられたー！
Whoa! We're done for!
イノセント・リバイバー！
Innocent Reviver!
信じるからね...！みんなの愛が... 力をくれる！
I'll believe in it...! Everyone's love... gives me strength!
ラミィちゃん、ナイス！それじゃあ、決めちゃうよ！
Lamy-chan, nice! Alright then, let's finish this!
ジュニペリア・ラミネーション！ フラッシュ・ストーム・コンプレッション！
Juniperus Lamination! Flash Storm Compression!
みこみこ先輩！
Miko-Miko Senior!
サンキュー、ルーナ！
Thank you, Luna!
触って！
Touch this!
テイク・リミット・スフィア！
Take Limit Sphere!
みんな、みこのエリートなところ、そんなに見たいんだー？
Does everyone really want to see my elite side that badly?
しょうがないねぇ！
Guess I have no choice!
みんなと一緒に！
Together with everyone!
んなまじっくなのだー！
That's Naa-Magic, nanoda!
セイバー・さくらりゅーむ・セイバー！
Saber Sakuraryum Saber!
プリンセス・セイバー！
Princess Saber!
スラッシュ・ヘイロー！
Slash Halo!
マリン！
Marine!
サンキュー、かなた！
Thank you, Kanata!
みんなの思い、全部のっけて、飛び込んでいくしかないだろー！
Carrying everyone's feelings, I just have to dive right in!
キミたち、ちょうど欲しいとこに来てくれるジャン！
You guys always show up right when I need you most!
みんな揃って、いいオタカラね！
All of you together are such fine treasures!
よっしゃー！
Alright!
やー！
Haaa!
セレスティアル・リンキング！
Celestial Linking!
オーバー・スプラッシュ・ガール！
Over Splash Girl!
あいつらでラストだ！
Those guys are the last ones!
いくよ、みんな！
Let's go, everyone!
チェンジ！
Change!
ホロウィッチ・ステッキ！
holoWitches Stick!
フルキャスト！
Full Cast!
ミオ先輩、もう大丈夫そう？
Mio-senpai, are you feeling okay now?
あ、うん！ その...見ないようにすればなんとか...
Ah, yeah! Um... as long as I try not to look, I can manage...
分かるよー！ 白上も高いところ行くと下見れないからねー！
I get it! Shirakami can't look down when she goes up high either!
ルーたんも、虫はなるべく見ないようにしてるのら！
Lootan tries not to look at bugs as much as possible too, nanora!
ありがとう、みんな！
Thank you, everyone!
みんなが助けてくれたみたいに、うちもみんなが辛い時、苦しい時があったら...
Just like you all helped me, whenever any of you are going through a tough or painful time...
絶対、絶対力になるから！
I promise I'll definitely, definitely be there to support you!
さて、これでめでたしめでたし
Now then, and they all lived happily ever after...
でもいいんだけど
...that would be fine and all, but...
みんな！
Everyone!
ホロウィッチの活躍
HoloWitch in action...
もっと見たいんじゃない？
...don't you want to see more of them?
だそうだけど
That's what they say, though.
え？こっち？こっち振るの？
Huh? Me? You're passing it to me?
え？あ、いや...
Huh? Ah, no...
やります！
We'll do it!
よーし、やるよーみんな！
Alright, let's do this, everyone!
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue,
海を目指して歩く
we walk towards the sea.
怖いものなんてない
There's nothing to be scared of,
僕らはもう一人じゃない
we're no longer alone.
大切な何かが
On that night when something important...
壊れたあの夜に
...was broken,
僕らは星を探して
we were looking for the stars,
一人で歩いていた
walking all alone.
ペルセウス座流星群
Did you see the Perseid meteor shower
君も見てただろうか
too?
僕らは元気でやってるよ
We're doing fine,
君は今どこにいるの？
where are you right now?
方法という悪魔に
Don't be possessed by the devil
とり憑かれないで
called "method,"
目的という大事なものを
and remember that important thing
思い出して
called "purpose."
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue,
海を目指して歩く
we walk towards the sea.
怖いものなんてない
There's nothing to be scared of,
僕らはもう一人じゃない
we're no longer alone.
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue,
海を目指して歩く
we walk towards the sea.
怖くても大丈夫
It's okay to be scared,
僕らはもう一人じゃない
we're no longer alone.
大切な何かが
On that night when something important...
壊れたあの夜に
...was broken,
僕らは君を探して
we were looking for you,
一人で歩いていた
walking all alone.
あの日から僕らは
Since that day, we've been
一人で海を目指す
heading for the sea alone,
約束のあの場所で
saying, "At that promised place,
必ずまた逢おうと
we'll definitely meet again."
世間という悪魔に
Don't be fooled by the devil
惑わされないで
called "society,"
自分だけが決めた答を
and remember the "answer"
思い出して
that you decided on yourself.
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue,
海を目指して歩く
we walk towards the sea.
怖いものなんてない
There's nothing to be scared of,
僕らはもう一人じゃない
we're no longer alone.
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue,
海を目指して歩く
we walk towards the sea.
怖くても大丈夫
It's okay to be scared,
僕らはもう一人じゃない
we're no longer alone.
煌めきのような
In a life that is
人生の中で
like a sparkle,
君に出逢えて
I'm really glad
僕は本当によかった
that I met you.
街を抜け海に出たら
When we leave the city and hit the sea,
次はどこを目指そうか
where should we head next?
僕らはまた出かけよう
Let's set out again
愛しいこの地球を
into this beloved world.
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue,
海を目指して歩く
as we walk towards the sea.
怖いものなんてない
There's nothing to be afraid of,
僕らはもう一人じゃない
we are no longer alone.
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue,
海を目指して歩く
as we walk towards the sea.
怖くても大丈夫
Even if it's scary, it's okay,
僕らはもう一人じゃない
we are no longer alone.
みんな、今日はありがとー！
Everyone, thank you so much for today!
最高に楽しいハロウィンだったよね、みんなー！
That was the most fun Halloween ever, wasn't it, everyone?
ちょっとアクシデントもあったけどさ、そういうのも含めていい思い出になったんじゃない？
There were a few accidents, but including all that, didn't it become a great memory?
なったー！
It did!
さて、そろそろお時間となってまいりましたが...
Now then, it's almost time to wrap up, but...
アンコール！ アンコール！
Encore! Encore!
それじゃあ、アンコールにお応えして...
Well then, in response to your encore...
この曲、歌っちゃうのらー！
Let's sing this song!
『はじまりの魔法 -charm-』！
"Beginning Magic -charm-"!
はじまりの魔法 -charm-
[Title: Beginning Magic -charm-]
君に魔法をかけるよ
I'll cast magic on you,
We can spell All your dreams
始まりを告げる 鐘の音が響く
The chimes ring out, announcing the beginning.
気づいたときがいつだって スタートラインなんだ
Whenever you realize it, that's your starting line.
誰のものでもなかった 夢を叶えるのは
Fulfilling a dream that belonged to no one else,
見つけたばかりの小さな 冒険の輝きだけ
it's only the brilliance of the small adventure you just found.
どうして私だけ うまくいかないんだろう
Why am I the only one who can't get things right?
自分以外のすべてが 眩しく見えるけど
Everything except myself looks so dazzling,
ねぇ 君に見つけてほしくて
but hey, I wanted you to find me...
なりたい私になる 今こそ
To become the person I want to be, right now!
そうだ 叶えたい 掴みたい 夢があるから
That's right, because I have dreams I want to fulfill and grasp,
塞ぎこんだ日のことも 連れて踏み出すんだ
I'll take even the gloomy days with me and step forward.
信じる力が 奇跡を起こすように
So that the power of believing creates miracles,
君に魔法をかけるよ
I'll cast magic on you,
We can spell All your dreams
叶わない願い それぞれが等しく
Desires that don't come true, each equal,
流れていく世界で 何を求めて
in a flowing world, what are we seeking
歩き続けてるんだろう
as we keep on walking?
いつまでもこのまま 迷うけど
Even if I stay lost like this forever,
君がくれたこの空が
this sky that you gave me...
見えない翼を くれたね
gave me invisible wings.
そうだ 照らしたい 届けたい 人がいるから
That's right, because there's someone I want to shine on and reach,
もう一人を置いてった 後悔にしないで
don't let leaving someone behind turn into regret.
そう決めたんだ 愛したい 答えたい
I've decided. I want to love, I want to answer,
自分自身の人生
my very own life.
正解なんて超えてこう 見たい景色の先へ
Let's go beyond "correct answers", to the scenery we want to see.
どんな場所でもいいよ
Any place is fine,
どんな姿でもいい
any appearance is fine,
追いかけたいんだ あの煌めきを
I want to chase after that sparkle!
希望を 光を 力を すべて抱きしめて
Embracing hope, light, power, and everything,
持っていこう
let's carry it forward!
ほら 繋げたい 広げたい 道があるから
Look, because there's a path I want to connect and expand,
ここから始まる物語を 一緒に
let's write the story that begins here together.
信じる力が 奇跡を起こすように
So that the power of believing creates miracles...
この手を握って ひとりじゃないから
Hold this hand, because you're not alone.
君に魔法をかけるよ
I'll cast a spell on you!
We cast a spell on your dream!!
最高のステージだったよ ホロウィッチ
That was the best stage ever, Holowitch.
本当本当！みんなお疲れ様！
Really, really! Good job, everyone!
カノンさん... あの、今日は本当にありがとうございました
Kanon-san... Um, thank you so much for today.
それで... あなたはどうしてユメオチとか僕たちのことを...
So... how do you know about Yumewochi and about us...?
私、前にユメオチして、君たちに助けられたことがあるんだ
I... was once consumed by Yumewochi and saved by you girls.
えー！？
What?!
だから、あの時の自分と同じようにユメオチして苦しんでいる誰かを見ると、放っておけなくて...
So, when I see someone suffering from Yumewochi like I did back then, I just can't ignore them...
あと、実は... 今日このステージに出ることにしたのも、君たちが出ると聞いたからなんだ。もう一度会えたらって思って
And actually... the reason I decided to perform on this stage today was because I heard you girls were performing. I thought I might be able to meet you again.
だから今日は... えっと... すごく嬉しかった！これからもがんばってね、ホロウィッチ
So today... um... I was really happy! Keep giving it your all from now on, Holowitch.
そ、それじゃあ...
W-Well then...
また... ぜひ、また！
See you... Please, let's meet again!
あの人自身がユメオチして、ホロウィッチに助けられていたから...
Since that person was saved by Holowitch after being consumed by Yumewochi...
知っていたんだ。ユメオチした時の辛さも、そんな時誰かが手を差し伸べてくれることの嬉しさも...
They knew. They knew the pain of suffering from Yumewochi, and the joy of having someone reach out a hand at a time like that...
そっか... ミコたちが少しでも誰かの力になれたら...
I see... If Miko and the others could be of even a little help to someone...
その誰かが、また別の誰かの力になってくれるんだね
Then that someone will become a source of strength for another someone, right?
そうだね。しかもさ、それだけじゃなくて、ウチらの力になってくれたりもするわけじゃん
That's right. And not only that, they even end up giving strength to us too.
あの人や、今日応援してくれたみんなみたいに
Just like that person, and everyone who supported us today.
それって...
That means...
それって、すっごく...
That's super...
すっごくトリィト！
Super Treat!
キラキラ 宝石みたいに輝いてる
Sparkling, shining like jewels,
夢の結晶 みんなの宝物
crystals of dreams are everyone's treasure.
時々見失っちゃうこともあるけど
Though sometimes we lose sight of them,
溢れ出した光が僕を呼んだんだよ
the overflowing light called out to me.
絶対 大丈夫
It's definitely okay.
ただまっすぐでいることも楽じゃない日もあるよね
There are days when staying true isn't easy either, right?
諦めも 苦しみも隠さなくていい
You don't have to hide giving up or suffering,
心解き放とう
let's set your heart free.
夢を歌おう 魔法に乗せて
Let's sing of dreams, carried on magic!
何度も立ち上がる 君と一緒に進んでいく
Rising up again and again, I'll move forward together with you.
夢は 夢は まだ終わらない
Dreams, dreams are not over yet!
未来を取り戻そう
Let's reclaim the future!
何度だって笑ってもう一回歩きはじめよう
Smiling time after time, let's take a step forward once more.
ホロウィッチ on your side
Holowitch on your side
夢の先へ
To what lies beyond dreams!
ワクワクするような日々と夢の結晶
Thrilling days and crystals of dreams,
思い出して魔法を唱えてみたら
if you remember and try chanting magic,
ドキドキするような君の物語
your heart-pounding story...
キラリキラリ出す日常
Everyday life starting to sparkle,
頑張ってみても
Even when I try my best,
上手くいかない日の方が
there seem to be more days
多く感じちゃったりするよね
when things just don't go right.
だけど不安も悲しみも抱えないで
But don't hold on to your anxieties and sadness,
ひとりじゃない
you're not alone.
希望の種を
If we sow the seeds of hope
明日に蒔いたら
for tomorrow,
一番に輝く綺麗なお花が咲くよ
a beautiful flower will bloom, shining brightest of all.
夢を 歌を
Carrying our dreams, our songs,
魔法に乗せて
on magic,
何度も立ち上がる
we'll rise up again and again,
君と一緒に進んでく
and move forward together with you.
夢は 夢は 終わらない
Our dreams, our dreams will never end,
未来を音に描こう
let me draw the future into sound.
何度だって
No matter how many times,
笑って
laugh,
もう一回
and once more,
歩き始めよう
let's start walking again.
ホロウィッチ おいでよ
Holowitches, come along,
夢の先へ
beyond our dreams!